<h1> <font color=#0c66c6>ABOUT US</font></h1><br/>
    <p>
    Qalam Movement which aims to Provide educations to every Pakistani, where volunteers teach students from unprivileged
    class living in slum areas These kids do not afford schools and their expenditures which lead them to become beggars further so the volunteers of Qalam movement go there places and teach
    those children so that they can be able to earn for themselves in a right way, and not only that we aim to
    provide modern education in Madaris as well So that their knowledge about the modern world remain relatable.
    </p>
    <h3><font color=#0c66c6>Noor School</font></h3>
       <p>Where out of school children of slum areas are taught by university students. These children are given modern
          educations and are taught a proper course just like any other private or government school.Furthermore, it's the aim of Qalam Movement that they will be given some technical education so that they can earn their livings.
    </p>
    <h3><font color=#0c66c6>Maddaris Chapter</font></h3>
    <p>
    Maddaris are the most marginalized  and ignored education sector in the country. Lack of modern education in these madrassahs is creating
    friction among different factions in the society and thus, hampering progress. To nurture properly,
    students studying in Maddaris need proper structure of modern education. So, our aim is to educate kids from these madaris and nurture them by providing them modern and technical
    education so that they can compete with the children of other sectors
    </p>
	 <h3><font color=#0c66c6>>Entrepreneurship</font</h3>
    <p>Third phase of Qalam Movement is comprised of entrepreneurship which is  planned to be initiated in the end of this year 2020. Society’s progress and
       economic prosperity is attached with the presence of enterprising youth.Enterprising youth open new vistas of development in every field. Qalam
       Movement is working day and night to promote entrepreneurship among the student. Opportunity and platform will be provided to ambitious youth and students to present their ideas in front of investors
    </p>


    <h3><font color=#0c66c6>Post Modern Education reforms</font></h3>
    <p>Educational system in the developed world, let alone the underdeveloped world is becoming obsolete in front of necessities of the post-modern world. Qalam
       Movement will, in its final phase work on the educational reforms in the whole country. School will be established in various area of the country. These schools will
       recruit school will extra ordinary talent and will promote them and provide with opportunities to excel in their respective field of talent. These students will be given
       exposure of the advancements in their particular field. Qalam Movement will extend a network of laboratory schools and liaison offices in every district of the
       country
    </p>






