<h1> <font color=#0c66c6>PRIVACY POLICY</font></h1><br/>
    <p> QalamMovement built the QalamMovement App as a free Application. This service is provided by QalamMovement at no cost and is intended for use as is. This Page is used to inform volunteers regarding our policies with this collection, use, and disclosure of personal information if anyone decided to use my service

    </p>
    <h3><font color=#0c66c6>Information Collection and Use:</font></h3>
       <p>For a better experience, while using our Service, I may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information. The information that I request will be retained on your device and is not collected by me in any way.
            The app does use third party services that may collect information used to identify you.
            Link to privacy policy of third party service providers used by the app
            Google Play Services
    </p>
    <h3><font color=#0c66c6>Security</font></h3>
    <p>I want to inform you that whenever you use my Service, This Log Data may include  all information about the volunteer and studetns , this information is kept secure.
Cookies

    </p>
	 <h3><font color=#0c66c6>links to other sites</font></h3>
    <p>we all linking you to other app,  but while doing that we will make sure your data is not shared with any other app, or any other source outside of app.
    </p>


    <h3><font color=#0c66c6>contact us</font>
    </h3>
    <p>
    </p>
    <h3><font color=#0c66c6>connection to Internet</font>
        </h3>
        <p>
        </p>
